Look at this here.
The poor cousin noticed me man and wants to make a with me.
This message makes us excited,
Uncle,
that life is not won.
Let's go to this
Poze's manager is going to give me a ride to buy a piece across town.
How is Boss Juninho?
It is?
He's been messing with Rogério and his Marcelo,
giving you the greatest talent there.
Man is bro the problem is with the carburetor same guy now we are trying
to see if he can fix the carburetor or if he has to buy a new one.
The Chevas saga continues.
Thirteen days already hooman has to say hello to us there right hooman he
was in live i was in hello there is a hello then instagram can talk?
Pastor Gonçalves.
Pastor Gonçalves we are together and today is fifty-third.
Ha ha ha.
But a carburetor like that new is a bump bordering on both.
I tell bro that this guy.
My goodness in heaven I can answer you tomorrow morning.
It was only valid until tomorrow.
So they fight all over the good Paulo that the chevas has heard.
Starts giving a redneck and earns a little money.
Oh,
I'm going to buy a new carburetor,
he wants it from Nike,
he doesn't want a penalty kick and if he doesn't give it a carburetor,
there won't be any other way.
Raining a lot instead of me complaining.
Dude do the best you can with what you got.
Can't go until the person calls her.
Dude uses the phone.
Speak brother,
how are you doing in peace.
Thank you dear we are together.
It saw?
So Milene,
how are you?
Everything's fine then just pass me by please.
If you are in need of truffle replacement everything in Peace the girls sales.
Well,
there's 6 here,
bro,
there's 6 left tomorrow I'll take you there so Cara,
gratitude there for warning bro.
1 smart way to do this is to reorganize,
take 1 place that is selling less,
put in the place,
you are selling more and so we make the management smarter.
Water not quantity.
is on
more?
1 farewell until tomorrow
Haha.